<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>British Politics - Tag - DAVID LIAO</title>
        <link>https://davidycliao.github.io/tags/british-politics/</link>
        <description>British Politics - Tag - DAVID LIAO</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 21:29:01 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://davidycliao.github.io/tags/british-politics/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Paper Presentation @ Chicago MPSA 2022</title>
    <link>https://davidycliao.github.io/2022/01/event1/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 21:29:01 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://davidycliao.github.io/2022/01/event1/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Electoral Reform and Disunited Polarization: Evidence from Legislative Roll Calls This article investigates the strategic (inter- and intra-) party positioning in response to an electoral system transition from single non-transferable vote (SNTV) to single-member districts (SMDs) by studying the electoral reform in Taiwan and provides empirical evidence to the following questions. Does the switch of electoral system from SNTV to SMDs mitigate political polarization among parties? Does it influence the intra-party unitedness (cohesiveness), and thus, change legislators’ ideological positioning?]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Party Misperception, Party-voter Incongruence and Political Distrust</title>
    <link>https://davidycliao.github.io/2022/11/misperception/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 21:29:01 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://davidycliao.github.io/2022/11/misperception/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The paper investigates how citizens&rsquo; misperception of party positions influences the perceived congruence between ideological preferences and positions of parties&rsquo; ideological position. We use a voter-level longitudinal data in the British Election Study in conjunction with data from the Chapel Hill Expert Survey (CHES). We take advantage of the panel structure of our data set and directly test two hypotheses relating to voters&rsquo; misperception of party positions relates to subjectively perceived incongruence, and the effect of perceived and actual incongruence on trust and satisfaction with politics.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
