<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Taiwan Politics - Tag - DAVID LIAO</title>
        <link>https://davidycliao.github.io/tags/taiwan-politics/</link>
        <description>Taiwan Politics - Tag - DAVID LIAO</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 21:29:01 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://davidycliao.github.io/tags/taiwan-politics/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Presentation @ Dublin COMPTEXT 2022</title>
    <link>https://davidycliao.github.io/2022/04/event2/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 21:29:01 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://davidycliao.github.io/2022/04/event2/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Factionalism and the Red Guards under Mao&rsquo;s China: Ideal Point Estimation Using Text Data In this paper, we design a new strain of text scaling method, Slogan-based Wordfish (Swordfish), that takes advantage of the facilitation of the TextRank algorithm to extract the most representative political slogans in a given context and estimates Bayesian Generalized Wordfish with those extracted text variables. We test this method using the case of the Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution in China and the historical archive of handwritten big-character posters and self-printed tabloids from 1954.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Presentation @ Montréal APSA 2022</title>
    <link>https://davidycliao.github.io/2022/04/event3/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 21:29:01 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://davidycliao.github.io/2022/04/event3/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Measuring Party Convergence on Parliamentary Question Keywords Understanding the positions of parties and legislators is key to conceptualizing party cohesion and their representation in most democracies. This study is to measure intra-party heterogeneity and variability in issue attention by looking at what and why legislators are more likely to oversight the ministry officials on one specific topic or another during the question time. We answer this question using the case of Taiwan Legislative Yuan, and data on written parliamentary questions through an electoral reform from 1993 to 2020.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
