<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Conference - Category - DAVID LIAO</title>
        <link>https://davidycliao.github.io/categories/conference/</link>
        <description>Conference - Category - DAVID LIAO</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 21:29:01 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://davidycliao.github.io/categories/conference/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Poster Presentation @ Washington University in St. Louis PolMeth XXXIX</title>
    <link>https://davidycliao.github.io/2022/05/event5/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 21:29:01 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://davidycliao.github.io/2022/05/event5/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Electoral Reform and Pork Barrel in Parliamentary Questions Measuring legislator behaviours and tendencies towards constituencies under different electoral systems is important. This paper quantitatively investigates this topic using the case of Taiwan Legislative Yuan and data on written parliamentary questions through an electoral reform from multi-member districts (MMD) to single-member districts (SMD). With existing labelled pork legislation, I train deep learning models using convolutional neural networks with an embedding layer extracted from Transformer BERT to detect pork-barrel features in parliamentary questions over time.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Paper Presentation @Vienna ECPR SG Parliarmment</title>
    <link>https://davidycliao.github.io/2023/06/event1/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 21:29:01 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://davidycliao.github.io/2023/06/event1/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Electoral Reform and Disunited Polarization: Evidence from Legislative Roll Calls This paper investigates how legislators respond to an electoral reform by adjusting their ideological positions with respect to co-partisans and rivals. Using data from Taiwan&rsquo;s legislative roll calls over 20 years, we study the extent to which partisan disagreement is influenced by the 2008 Taiwanese electoral reform from Single Non-Transferable Votes (SNTV) to Single-Member Districts (SMD). Contrary to the literature, our empirical evidence shows that the reform significantly fragmented legislator positions in relation to both co-partisans and members from the rival party.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
