<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>NLP - Tag - DAVID LIAO</title>
        <link>https://davidycliao.github.io/tags/nlp/</link>
        <description>NLP - Tag - DAVID LIAO</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 21:29:01 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://davidycliao.github.io/tags/nlp/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>flairR: An R Wrapper for Accessing Flair NLP Tagging Features</title>
    <link>https://davidycliao.github.io/2023/06/pkg/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 21:29:01 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://davidycliao.github.io/2023/06/pkg/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[FlaiR - R wrapper for Flair NLP We are currently in the process of testing our package, which is an R wrapper designed specifically for Flair NLP. This package is tailored to provide core sequence tagging features, including part-of-speech tasks, named entity recognition, and transformer-based sentiment analysis.
One notable feature of our package is its ability to directly return a dataframe, which can be particularly useful for researchers in social or political science.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Co-authored Paper Presentation @Glasgow EPSA  </title>
    <link>https://davidycliao.github.io/2023/06/ccp/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 21:29:01 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://davidycliao.github.io/2023/06/ccp/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Electoral Systems and Party Convergence on Issue Attentions (with Yu-Ceng Liao) This paper investigates how legislators respond to an electoral reform by adjusting their ideological positions with respect to co-partisans and rivals. Using data from Taiwan&rsquo;s legislative roll calls over 20 years, we study the extent to which partisan disagreement is influenced by the 2008 Taiwanese electoral reform from Single Non-Transferable Votes (SNTV) to Single-Member Districts (SMD). Contrary to the literature, our empirical evidence shows that the reform significantly fragmented legislator positions in relation to both co-partisans and members from the rival party.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
