<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Working Paper - Category - DAVID LIAO</title>
        <link>https://davidycliao.github.io/categories/working-paper/</link>
        <description>Working Paper - Category - DAVID LIAO</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 21:29:01 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://davidycliao.github.io/categories/working-paper/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Factionalism and the Red Guards under Mao&#39;s China: Ideal Point Estimation Using Text Data</title>
    <link>https://davidycliao.github.io/2022/04/redgaurds/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 21:29:01 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://davidycliao.github.io/2022/04/redgaurds/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we design a new strain of text scaling method, Swordfish (Slogan-featured Wordfish), that takes advantage of the TextRank algorithm to extract the most representative political slogans in a given context and estimates Wordfish with those extracted text variables. We test this method using the case of the Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution in China and the historical archive of handwritten big-character posters and self-printed tabloids from 1966. We estimate student protests&rsquo; ideal points by analyzing expressed political views in propaganda publications.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>The Role of Rituals in Adversarial Parliaments: An Analysis of Expressions of Collegiality in the British House of Commons</title>
    <link>https://davidycliao.github.io/2023/01/ritual/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 21:29:01 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://davidycliao.github.io/2023/01/ritual/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Despite the adversarial character of debates in the British House of Commons, Members of Parliament (MPs) observe a highly ritualized rhetorical style emphasizing collegiality and mutual respect across party lines. The language MPs use in this context harks back to an ancient pre-democratic past. Why does a modern democratic legislature conceal partisan conflict by using pre-democratic ritualistic references to the House' as a corporate actor? Why do they call their fiercest competitors honourable Members&rsquo; or even `Friends&rsquo;?]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
